

19/04/1999

## CONTACT

- +84 (03)67 005 758
- tutinhxomdong3@gmail.com
- Chua Lang, Dong Da, Ha Noi

## **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2022 LE QUY DON TECHNICAL **UNIVERSITY (HA NOI)** 

- Software Engineering
- CPA: 2.9

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Quality Check

## **PASTIMES**

• In my free time, I work on some e-commerce website projects, read books, exercise and go experience things

# **NGUYEN TU TINH**

## **DEVELOPER**

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm a web developer with 1.5 years of experience in NodeJS technologies, with knowledge of Object-Oriented Analysis and Design, and Database Design. Persistent in self-studying and learning new technologies, self-motivated, hardworking, responsible, and reliable, working effectively both independently and as a part of the team.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **AKB Software**

Full Stack Developer

08/2022 - PRESENT

- I do outsourcing projects from Japan with different technologies.
- I participate in upgrading and maintaining a number of functional modules for a few domestic projects such as NS2HN management system, ADVSCM conference equipment control system.
- In addition, I am also a key developer for the ChungVui product project to create online invitations for user events, with the task of capturing the work of other team members and ensuring project quality

#### **Antbot Vietnam Company**

2021 - 2022

Junior Developer

- Participate in the project of Building a Military Science management support system of the General Department of Technology
- In addition, during this time I completed the graduation project on a dictionary lookup website combined with OCR using the FARM Stack.

## TECHNICAL SKILL

- Programming Language: JavaScript, Java, HTML5, CSS3
- Frameworks/Flatforms: ReactJS, TailwindCSS, NodeJS, Web API, GraphQL
- Database Management Systems: PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Version Control: SVN, Git
- Foreign Language: English (Basics- 500 Toeic)
- Others: CI/CD of GitLab. Scrum development process